<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vyper on Second State News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/vyper/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vyper on Second State News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 20:01:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/vyper/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State 又获以太坊生态体系的资助奖励</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200217-soll-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200217-soll-zh/</guid>
      <description>Second State 最近获得了以太坊生态最大的去中心化自治组织（DAO） Panvala 的资助奖励。Panvala 由 ConsenSys 创立孵化，为以太坊生态里最重要的基础软件项目提供资金</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State receives another grant award for the SOLL compiler</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200216-soll-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200216-soll-en/</guid>
      <description>Second State has been awarded a development grant from Panvala, a leading DAO (Decentralized Autonomous Organization) in the Ethereum ecosystem.
Founded at ConsenSys, Panvala provides funding support for critical software development efforts in the Ethereum ecosystem. Past Panvala grant awardees include Sigma Prime, Prysmatic Labs, MakerDAO, Aragon, Status, and Gitcoin.
Prior to the Panvala grant, Second State is already a recognized leader in Ethereum infrastructure development. It is had received funding and prizes from both the Ethereum Foundation and Ethereum Classic Labs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diving into Ethereum&#39;s Virtual Machine(EVM): the future of Ewasm</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191029-ewasm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191029-ewasm/</guid>
      <description>Ethereum is a blockchain with a built-in Turing-complete programming language. It allows anyone to create a decentralised application, by making use of Ethereum smart contracts.
 “The Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) is the part of Ethereum that handles smart contract deployment and execution” (Antonopoulos and Wood, 2018).
 The EVM consists of a stack-based architecture. In order for a smart contract to be deployed, all high level Ethereum smart contract code must first be compiled into machine-readable code (called bytecode).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>深度剖析以太坊虚拟机（EVM）的未来：Ewasm</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191029-ewasm-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191029-ewasm-zh/</guid>
      <description>以太坊是具有内置图灵完备编程语言的区块链。任何人都可以使用以太坊智能合约来创建去中心化应用程序。 “以太坊虚拟机（EVM）是以太坊处理智能合约</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>