<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>developer on Second State News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/categories/developer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in developer on Second State News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 09:42:14 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.secondstate.io/categories/developer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Toward a more interoperable WebAssembly</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201026-toward-a-more-interoperable-webassembly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201026-toward-a-more-interoperable-webassembly/</guid>
      <description>Reference types and bulk memory operations support on Second State VM 0.7.0
The Second State VM (SSVM) is an open-source WebAssembly virtual machine implementation optimized for server-side applications.
 It is one of the fastest WebAssembly VM on the market today partly because of AOT (Ahead Of Time) compiler optimization. See our performance benchmark paper to be published on IEEE Software. It provides seamless integration into population web service frameworks, such as Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling All Developers: Second State Launches BUIDL IDE, an Integrated Development Environment Software Application, for Ethereum Classic Blockchain</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190925-buidl-for-etc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190925-buidl-for-etc/</guid>
      <description>This news is also seen on PRweb.com
 SAN FRANCISCO (Sept. 24, 2019) —Second State, developer of an open source, blockchain-based smart contract platform for global business, has announced the launch of its BUIDL IDE, an integrated development environment software application for Ethereum Classic (ETC), the preeminent blockchain for smart contracts and “dapps.” With Second State’s BUIDL IDE, development and deployment on ETC can be done within minutes, from any web browser: secondstate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>如何使用BUIDL 发布一个自己的区块链网站</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190920-blockchain-programming-guide-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190920-blockchain-programming-guide-zh/</guid>
      <description>欢迎来到区块链的世界，在区块链应用里，您留下的足迹会永远留存，永远不会消失~ 小科普 区块链应用通常以智能合约为后端，以HTML 和 JavaScr</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetup#7：Libra 智能合约技术详解</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190805-meetup-deep-dive-with-libra-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190805-meetup-deep-dive-with-libra-zh/</guid>
      <description>Libra 在国会听证后，该何去何从？ 在Libra 开发与在以太坊上开发有什么不同？ ERC 20 token 能否在Libra 上做交互？ 如何快速入手DApp 开发？ 8月3日，</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Contract Meetup 7:  Libra Deep Dive</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190805-libra-deep-dive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190805-libra-deep-dive/</guid>
      <description>With Libra being scrutinized, if not attacked, at Congressional hearing, where is the anticipated ambitious global stable coin is heading towards?
  What is the difference between the programming on Libra and Ethereum?
  Can ERC 20 token interact with Libra?
  How to get started with DApp programming in a few minutes?
  These are discussed in detail at the tech workshop &amp;ldquo;Libra Smart Contract Deep Dive&amp;rdquo; held in Beijing, China, on August 3rd.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>