<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ethereum on Second State News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/categories/ethereum/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ethereum on Second State News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 09:42:14 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.secondstate.io/categories/ethereum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>只需 5 分钟，教你如何编写并执行一个 Rust &#43; WebAssembly 程序</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191220-rust-webassembly-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191220-rust-webassembly-zh/</guid>
      <description>在探讨 WASM 在服务端的巨大潜力时，我们提到 WASM 的一大优势就是支持有影响力的新锐编程语言，例如 Rust 。这篇文章将展示如何编写并执行一个 Wasm Rust 程序，只有代码</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Ethereum Development A2Z| Smart Contract ABI </title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191118-ethereum-developer-abi-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191118-ethereum-developer-abi-en/</guid>
      <description>Learn Ethereum development and acquire complex technical concepts in a snap!
Second State Inc is to release Ethereum development A2Z series articles to help you learn Ethereum in a short time starting from the basics, with real blockchain development cases.
This article is to introduce Smart Contract ABI, the first piece in the series.
Blockchain Smart Contract ABI is the interface between smart contracts and blockchain applications. After a smart contract is compiled into a binary file by a compiler like BUIDL, an ABI for this smart contract is automatically generated, recording the functions and parameters of the smart contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ABI | 以太坊开发A2Z </title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191112-ethereum-developer-abi-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191112-ethereum-developer-abi-zh/</guid>
      <description>快速了解以太坊开发，快速 get 复杂的技术概念！ Second State 推出以太坊开发A2Z 系列，结合区块链开发的实际情况，带你了解以太坊开发的点点面面。 这篇文章是该</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ewasm Vs EVM：Ewasm 带来了什么改变？</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191106-ewasm-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191106-ewasm-zh/</guid>
      <description>这篇文章是 Crosslink 2019 Taiwan 的一个议程纪录：The next generation Ethereum Virtual Machine，由来自Second State 的工程VP Hung-Ying Tai（hydai） 分享 Ewasm VM 目前研究内容及未来</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>一文带你了解Devcon5</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191025-devcon5-recap-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191025-devcon5-recap-zh/</guid>
      <description>以太坊基金会 Devcon 是以太坊生态系统中最重要的开发者、设计师和研究人员的年度聚会。今年在日本大阪举行的 Devcon5 是第五届以太开发大会，与往年一样，Devc</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State receives a prestigious award from the Ethereum Foundation for the SOLL compiler</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191022-soll-compiler-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191022-soll-compiler-project/</guid>
      <description>(Oct 20th, 2019, Taipei) - Second State, a leading provider of open source infrastructure software for blockchain smart contracts, has been awarded a cash prize for its contribution to the open source SOLL compiler project. Vitalik Buterin from the Ethereum Foundation presented Hung-Ying Tai from Second State with the $5000 prize at the CrossLink event in Taipei on Oct 20th, 2019.
SOLL is the world’s first toolchain that compiles Solidity smart contracts into WebAssembly bytecode and successfully deploys onto Ethereum Foundation’s official Ewasm (Ethereum flavored WebAssembly) testnet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State SOLL 编译器项目获得以太坊基金会的现金奖励</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191022-soll-compiler-project-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191022-soll-compiler-project-zh/</guid>
      <description>Second State 是领先的面向区块链智能合约的开源基础架构软件的提供者，因为对开源SOLL编译器项目的贡献，获得了以太坊基金会的现金奖励。2019年10月</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State 发布专为以太经典（ETC）打造的BUIDL IDE工具</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190926-buidl-for-etc-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190926-buidl-for-etc-zh/</guid>
      <description>区块链智能合约平台Second State 发布专为以太经典（Ethereum Classic）打造的BUIDL IDE。BUIDL 集成了以太经典开发环境，</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling All Developers: Second State Launches BUIDL IDE, an Integrated Development Environment Software Application, for Ethereum Classic Blockchain</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190925-buidl-for-etc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190925-buidl-for-etc/</guid>
      <description>This news is also seen on PRweb.com
 SAN FRANCISCO (Sept. 24, 2019) —Second State, developer of an open source, blockchain-based smart contract platform for global business, has announced the launch of its BUIDL IDE, an integrated development environment software application for Ethereum Classic (ETC), the preeminent blockchain for smart contracts and “dapps.” With Second State’s BUIDL IDE, development and deployment on ETC can be done within minutes, from any web browser: secondstate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Classic partners with Second State to build the next generation Ethereum infrastructure</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190901-etc-partners-with-secondstate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190901-etc-partners-with-secondstate/</guid>
      <description>Ethereum Classic Labs (ETC Labs), the developer and maintainer of the Ethereum Classic blockchain (ETC), announced today that it has entered a partnership with a leading blockchain infrastructure developer, Second State, to create open source toolchain and runtime software that powers the next generation of Ethereum-compatible blockchains, including the Ethereum Classic.
This partnership will bring high-impact enhancements into the ETC ecosystem, and make the ETC blockchain a premier destination for smart contract developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EDCON 2019 — The annual community Ethereum development conference</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190419-edcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190419-edcon/</guid>
      <description>EDCON2019 EDCON 2019 kicked off, in Sydney Australia, with a pleasantly surprising ice breaker. Vitalik Buterin, Karl Floersch and Co. captured the audience with a live on-stage hip-hop performance; waxing lyrical about eth2.0, merkle proofs, plasma chains, zkSNARKs, eWASM and account abstraction.
The upbeat and playful community atmosphere continued throughout the entire conference. The days were not only filled with conference presentations. They were filled with lively community interactions, the sharing of ideas, collaborative coding opportunities and even physical puzzle challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>