<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>en on Second State News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/categories/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in en on Second State News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 01:01:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.secondstate.io/categories/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WasmEdge (formerly SSVM) is now a CNCF Project</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/wasmedge-ssvm-joins-cncf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/wasmedge-ssvm-joins-cncf/</guid>
      <description>We are thrilled to announce that WasmEdge, formerly SSVM, has recently been accepted by the CNCF Foundation as a sandbox project, which is the first offcial CNCF WebAssembly runtime project. We envision that it will fill an important role in CNCF’s open source cloud computing landscape as a mission critical lightweight runtime for edge clouds.
For more infomation about WasmEdge, check out this article.
Join the WasmEdge Community:
👉 GitHub:WasmEdge</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The SSVM 0.7 release brings WebAssembly to the public cloud</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20210202-ssvm-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 06:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20210202-ssvm-release/</guid>
      <description>The SSVM (Second State VM) is a popular WebAssembly VM optimized for high-performance applications on the server side. With advanced AOT (Ahead of Time compiler) support, the SSVM is already one of the fastest WebAssembly VMs. The recent SSVM release 0.7 brings a wide array of unique features that further differentiate and solidify the SSVM as a leading cloud native application runtime.
WebAssembly proposals The SSVM supports optional WebAssembly features and proposals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State Functions releases a developer preview for high performance serverless functions</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20210114-second-state-functions-developer-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 06:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20210114-second-state-functions-developer-preview/</guid>
      <description>Second State has recently released a developer preview of its Function-as-a-Service (FaaS), known as Second State Functions. The Second State Functions enables developers to write simple functions in the Rust programming language for computationally intensive tasks such as image processing and AI inference. The developer simply needs to upload the compiled function to the FaaS service, and the function will become publically available as a web service. The developer preview version of the Second State Functions is free to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State partners with Oasis Foundation and Gitcoin to host The Quest for ROSE</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201109-secondstate-oasis-gitcoin-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 06:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201109-secondstate-oasis-gitcoin-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>Developers rejoice! A new week, a new hackathon with great prizes!
The Oasis Foundation announced the Quest for ROSE: An Oasis Network Hackathon in partnership with Gitcoin and Second State from 9th November to 2nd December.
There are two challenges for the Quest for ROSE hackathon. One is to use Parcel SDK of Oasis Network to develop responsible data apps. The other one is to use Oasis Ethereum ParaTimeto develop ethereum-compatible Dapps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developers created 3274 smart contracts in the Oasis Second State Hackathon</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201029-recap-the-oasis-second-state-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 06:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201029-recap-the-oasis-second-state-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>Oasis Foundation and Second State partnered on a community hackathon from 12th to 23rd Oct to bring Ethereum developers to the Oasis Ethereum ParaTime. Now, the results are in! Community developers created 3274 smart contracts and published 759 decentralized web apps in 11 days!
The Oasis Second State Hackathon set up three challenges for developers to complete. When developers complete any of the challenges, they get ROSE (the native token of the Oasis network) as rewards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toward a more interoperable WebAssembly</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201026-toward-a-more-interoperable-webassembly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201026-toward-a-more-interoperable-webassembly/</guid>
      <description>Interface types and bulk memory operations support on Second State VM 0.7.0
 TL;DR Second State is committed to support the vision of WebAssembly nanoprocess proposed by Bytecode Alliance, Fastly, and Mozilla. SSVM 0.7.0 implements two key components of nanoprocess: WASI and Interface Types. We are taking it further with WASI-like extensions for blockchains and Tensorflow. Try our Tensorflow as a Service live demo today!
 The Second State VM (SSVM) is an open-source WebAssembly virtual machine implementation optimized for server-side applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Oasis Second State Community Hackathon starts</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/oasis-secondstate-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/oasis-secondstate-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>Today Second State, together with Oasis foundation, is announcing the most exciting community event to date, and a chance for community members to earn some of the largest rewards Oasis foundation has ever offered. Last week Oasis network launched Mainnet Beta, and we released Second State’s Oasis Ethereum ParaTime.
The ParaTime’s powerful design and technology means the Oasis Ethereum ParaTime is:
 Completely backward compatible with Ethereum with support for the entire Solidity toolchain, allowing it to support DApps currently on the Ethereum network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State releases scalable privacy service at Mozilla Open Labs</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200603-scalable-privacy-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200603-scalable-privacy-service/</guid>
      <description>Building a scalable and privacy-first Internet on Second State’s serverless infrastructure. Get the email newsletter on Rust, WebAssembly, serverless, blockchain, and AI.
Internet privacy is broken The Public Key Infrastructure (PKI), invented over 40 years ago, has been the bed rock for security and privacy on the Internet. While PKI algorithms are behind the most internet security protocols, such as HTTPS and TLS, the idea for individuals to use public keys to exchange data, (eg, PGP), was not adopted in large scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Rust</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200529-why-rust-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 19:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200529-why-rust-en/</guid>
      <description>The Rust programming language is gaining popularity amongst developers. For 5 years in a row, it is voted as the most beloved programming language in the world. In the most recent 2020 survey of 65,000 developers, Rust was beloved by a stunning 86.1% of developers. Being loved by developers is a leading indicator that Rust is on the path of mass adoption. It is entering a positive feedback cycle of more developers, more libraries, better tools, larger talent pool, more adoption, and then more developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State released SSVM version 0.5.0 for the new generation Ethereum virtual machine Ewasm</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200416-ewasm-smart-contract-ssvm-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200416-ewasm-smart-contract-ssvm-en/</guid>
      <description>The Ethereum flavored WebAssembly (Ewasm) virtual machine is a key infrastructure component of the next generation Ethereum (Ethereum 2.0) ecosystem. Second State recently released a new version of its leading Ewasm software, empowering developers to write tomorrow’s Ethereum 2.0 smart contracts today!
The Second State Virtual Machine (SSVM) is a high-performance, server-optimized WebAssembly runtime. SSVM supports multiple WebAssembly extensions, including Ewasm. In the recently released SSVM 0.5.0 software, the SSVM-evmc extension specially supports Ewasm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State joins Microsoft for Startups to develop the next generation software infrastructure for cloud computing</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200325-microsoft-for-startups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200325-microsoft-for-startups/</guid>
      <description>Second State joins the Microsoft for Startups program to develop and commercialize the next generation software infrastructure for cloud computing. With Microsoft for Startups, Second State will create open source software frameworks and developer tools for the cloud and for blockchains based on the WebAssembly technology.
WebAssembly was originally created as a high-performance execution engine for web browsers. As it becomes increasingly popular in the developer community, WebAssembly is moving from the client-side to the server-side, powering the next generation cloud services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polkadot is getting WebAssembly-based Ethereum 2.0 virtual machine from Second State</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200302-polkadot-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200302-polkadot-en/</guid>
      <description>Polkadot’s founder, Dr. Gavin Wood, is one of the original architects of the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM). Dr. Wood, the co-author of “Mastering Ethereum”, is also the author of the Ethereum yellow paper; a formal definition of the Ethereum protocol (in mathematical terms), which also provides an in-depth explanation of how the EVM actually works.
Some may be aware that the Polkadot ecosystem did not initially come with a Turing-complete virtual machine like the EVM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State awarded a grant to bring next-gen Ethereum infrastructure to Polkadot ecosystem</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200228-polkadot-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200228-polkadot-en/</guid>
      <description>(02/28/2020, Austin TX USA)The Web3 Foundation has awarded Second State, a leading cloud and blockchain infrastructure company, a grant to bring the Ethereum flavored WebAssembly (Ewasm) virtual machine to the Polkadot ecosystem. Get this project from GitHub here: https://github.com/second-state/substrate-ewasm
The virtual machine is a key infrastructure component for public blockchains. It allows any user from the public to submit untrusted code to the blockchain platform, in the form of smart contracts, and pay for its execution based on resource consumption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State receives another grant award for the SOLL compiler</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200216-soll-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200216-soll-en/</guid>
      <description>Second State has been awarded a development grant from Panvala, a leading DAO (Decentralized Autonomous Organization) in the Ethereum ecosystem.
Founded at ConsenSys, Panvala provides funding support for critical software development efforts in the Ethereum ecosystem. Past Panvala grant awardees include Sigma Prime, Prysmatic Labs, MakerDAO, Aragon, Status, and Gitcoin.
Prior to the Panvala grant, Second State is already a recognized leader in Ethereum infrastructure development. It is had received funding and grants from both the Ethereum Foundation and Ethereum Classic Labs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State releases WebAssembly for the server side</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191218-webassembly-for-the-server-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191218-webassembly-for-the-server-side/</guid>
      <description>An open source WebAssembly runtime optimized for blockchain, AI, and cloud services
(12/17/2019, Taipei)The Second State team has released a “developer preview” of the Second State Virtual Machine (SSVM). It is a WebAssembly (Wasm) compatible runtime engineered from ground up for server side applications. Get it from Github here: https://github.com/second-state/SSVM
Wasm started as a high performance execution engine inside web browsers. It is language agnostic (supporting popular new languages such as Rust), platform agnostic, lightweight, fast, and also provides native hardware access through its modular security model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebAssembly on the server side</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191124-wasm-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 19:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191124-wasm-en/</guid>
      <description>WebAssembly (Wasm), originally invented and developed by Mozilla, Google, Microsoft, Apple, and others at W3C; is a high-performance execution engine for in-browser web applications. As it gains popularity on the client-side, Wasm is also becoming a serious contender as a server-side technology.
Value propositions of WebAssembly Wasm’s move from client-side to server-side follows well-traveled paths of previous generations of technologies such as Java and JavaScript. Compared with existing solutions, Wasm offers some compelling value propositions on the server-side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Ethereum Development A2Z| Smart Contract ABI </title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191118-ethereum-developer-abi-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191118-ethereum-developer-abi-en/</guid>
      <description>Learn Ethereum development and acquire complex technical concepts in a snap!
Second State Inc is to release Ethereum development A2Z series articles to help you learn Ethereum in a short time starting from the basics, with real blockchain development cases.
This article is to introduce Smart Contract ABI, the first piece in the series.
Blockchain Smart Contract ABI is the interface between smart contracts and blockchain applications. After a smart contract is compiled into a binary file by a compiler like BUIDL, an ABI for this smart contract is automatically generated, recording the functions and parameters of the smart contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Next Generation Ethereum Virtual Machine — Ewasm VM</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191106-ewasm-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191106-ewasm-en/</guid>
      <description>The next generation Ethereum Virtual Machine — Crosslink 2019 Taiwan This is a wrap-up for Second State’s VP of Engineering, Mr. Hung-Ying Tai’s presentation on SOLL, Ewasm VM&#39;s current research content and future direction. The sharing is very exciting, including content on EVM bytecode, Webassembly, Ewasm1.0 and Ewasm2.0 EVM bytecode and Webassembly (WASM) When Ethereum&#39;s smart contract transaction is executed,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrate Halloween with Blockchain Smart Contract</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191031-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191031-halloween/</guid>
      <description>Halloween is finally here! Are you ready for the spookiest night of the year?
BUIDL IDE tools now has an upgraded UI just for Halloween. Trick or treat! A spooky pumpkin on the top welcomes you to the BUIDL’s Halloween.
Now, for developers, can you tell what the following code is for?
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8  pragma lity ^1.2.4; contract Halloween { function greet() pure public returns (string) { return &amp;#34;Happy Halloween&amp;#34;; } }   This is a very simple (yet spooky) smart contract example, just like the “Hello World” on the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diving into Ethereum&#39;s Virtual Machine(EVM): the future of Ewasm</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191029-ewasm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191029-ewasm/</guid>
      <description>Ethereum is a blockchain with a built-in Turing-complete programming language. It allows anyone to create a decentralised application, by making use of Ethereum smart contracts.
 “The Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) is the part of Ethereum that handles smart contract deployment and execution” (Antonopoulos and Wood, 2018).
 The EVM consists of a stack-based architecture. In order for a smart contract to be deployed, all high level Ethereum smart contract code must first be compiled into machine-readable code (called bytecode).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>