<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>confidential smart contract on Second State News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/confidential-smart-contract/</link>
    <description>Recent content in confidential smart contract on Second State News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 06:42:14 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/confidential-smart-contract/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State partners with Oasis Foundation and Gitcoin to host The Quest for ROSE</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201109-secondstate-oasis-gitcoin-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 06:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201109-secondstate-oasis-gitcoin-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>Developers rejoice! A new week, a new hackathon with great prizes!
The Oasis Foundation announced the Quest for ROSE: An Oasis Network Hackathon in partnership with Gitcoin and Second State from 9th November to 2nd December.
There are two challenges for the Quest for ROSE hackathon. One is to use Parcel SDK of Oasis Network to develop responsible data apps. The other one is to use Oasis Ethereum ParaTimeto develop ethereum-compatible Dapps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developers created 3274 smart contracts in the Oasis Second State Hackathon</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201029-recap-the-oasis-second-state-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 06:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201029-recap-the-oasis-second-state-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>Oasis Foundation and Second State partnered on a community hackathon from 12th to 23rd Oct to bring Ethereum developers to the Oasis Ethereum ParaTime. Now, the results are in! Community developers created 3274 smart contracts and published 759 decentralized web apps in 11 days!
The Oasis Second State Hackathon set up three challenges for developers to complete. When developers complete any of the challenges, they get ROSE (the native token of the Oasis network) as rewards.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>