<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ethereum on Second State News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/ethereum/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ethereum on Second State News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 06:42:14 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/ethereum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State Functions releases a developer preview for high performance serverless functions</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20210114-second-state-functions-developer-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 06:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20210114-second-state-functions-developer-preview/</guid>
      <description>Second State has recently released a developer preview of its Function-as-a-Service (FaaS), known as Second State Functions. The Second State Functions enables developers to write simple functions in the Rust programming language for computationally intensive tasks such as image processing and AI inference. The developer simply needs to upload the compiled function to the FaaS service, and the function will become publically available as a web service. The developer preview version of the Second State Functions is free to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State partners with Oasis Foundation and Gitcoin to host The Quest for ROSE</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201109-secondstate-oasis-gitcoin-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 06:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201109-secondstate-oasis-gitcoin-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>Developers rejoice! A new week, a new hackathon with great prizes!
The Oasis Foundation announced the Quest for ROSE: An Oasis Network Hackathon in partnership with Gitcoin and Second State from 9th November to 2nd December.
There are two challenges for the Quest for ROSE hackathon. One is to use Parcel SDK of Oasis Network to develop responsible data apps. The other one is to use Oasis Ethereum ParaTimeto develop ethereum-compatible Dapps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developers created 3274 smart contracts in the Oasis Second State Hackathon</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201029-recap-the-oasis-second-state-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 06:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201029-recap-the-oasis-second-state-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>Oasis Foundation and Second State partnered on a community hackathon from 12th to 23rd Oct to bring Ethereum developers to the Oasis Ethereum ParaTime. Now, the results are in! Community developers created 3274 smart contracts and published 759 decentralized web apps in 11 days!
The Oasis Second State Hackathon set up three challenges for developers to complete. When developers complete any of the challenges, they get ROSE (the native token of the Oasis network) as rewards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Oasis Second State Community Hackathon starts</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/oasis-secondstate-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/oasis-secondstate-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>Today Second State, together with Oasis foundation, is announcing the most exciting community event to date, and a chance for community members to earn some of the largest rewards Oasis foundation has ever offered. Last week Oasis network launched Mainnet Beta, and we released Second State’s Oasis Ethereum ParaTime.
The ParaTime’s powerful design and technology means the Oasis Ethereum ParaTime is:
 Completely backward compatible with Ethereum with support for the entire Solidity toolchain, allowing it to support DApps currently on the Ethereum network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>奖励最高达 31050 ROSE, Oasis &#43; Second State 线上 Hackathon 正式开始</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/oasis-secondstate-hackathon-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/oasis-secondstate-hackathon-zh/</guid>
      <description>发布Dapp，在 Oasis network 上运行以太坊智能合约，就可以获得 ROSE Token 奖励 Oasis Network 是隐私计算领域的知名项目，10月2日，Oasis 基金会发布了 Mainnet beta 版以及由 Second State</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State released SSVM version 0.5.0 for the new generation Ethereum virtual machine Ewasm</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200416-ewasm-smart-contract-ssvm-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200416-ewasm-smart-contract-ssvm-en/</guid>
      <description>The Ethereum flavored WebAssembly (Ewasm) virtual machine is a key infrastructure component of the next generation Ethereum (Ethereum 2.0) ecosystem. Second State recently released a new version of its leading Ewasm software, empowering developers to write tomorrow’s Ethereum 2.0 smart contracts today!
The Second State Virtual Machine (SSVM) is a high-performance, server-optimized WebAssembly runtime. SSVM supports multiple WebAssembly extensions, including Ewasm. In the recently released SSVM 0.5.0 software, the SSVM-evmc extension specially supports Ewasm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polkadot is getting WebAssembly-based Ethereum 2.0 virtual machine from Second State</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200302-polkadot-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200302-polkadot-en/</guid>
      <description>Polkadot’s founder, Dr. Gavin Wood, is one of the original architects of the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM). Dr. Wood, the co-author of “Mastering Ethereum”, is also the author of the Ethereum yellow paper; a formal definition of the Ethereum protocol (in mathematical terms), which also provides an in-depth explanation of how the EVM actually works.
Some may be aware that the Polkadot ecosystem did not initially come with a Turing-complete virtual machine like the EVM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State awarded a grant to bring next-gen Ethereum infrastructure to Polkadot ecosystem</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200228-polkadot-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200228-polkadot-en/</guid>
      <description>(02/28/2020, Austin TX USA)The Web3 Foundation has awarded Second State, a leading cloud and blockchain infrastructure company, a grant to bring the Ethereum flavored WebAssembly (Ewasm) virtual machine to the Polkadot ecosystem. Get this project from GitHub here: https://github.com/second-state/substrate-ewasm
The virtual machine is a key infrastructure component for public blockchains. It allows any user from the public to submit untrusted code to the blockchain platform, in the form of smart contracts, and pay for its execution based on resource consumption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State 又获以太坊生态体系的资助奖励</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200217-soll-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200217-soll-zh/</guid>
      <description>Second State 最近获得了以太坊生态最大的去中心化自治组织（DAO） Panvala 的资助奖励。Panvala 由 ConsenSys 创立孵化，为以太坊生态里最重要的基础软件项目提供资金</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State receives another grant award for the SOLL compiler</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200216-soll-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200216-soll-en/</guid>
      <description>Second State has been awarded a development grant from Panvala, a leading DAO (Decentralized Autonomous Organization) in the Ethereum ecosystem.
Founded at ConsenSys, Panvala provides funding support for critical software development efforts in the Ethereum ecosystem. Past Panvala grant awardees include Sigma Prime, Prysmatic Labs, MakerDAO, Aragon, Status, and Gitcoin.
Prior to the Panvala grant, Second State is already a recognized leader in Ethereum infrastructure development. It is had received funding and grants from both the Ethereum Foundation and Ethereum Classic Labs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Ethereum Development A2Z| Smart Contract ABI </title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191118-ethereum-developer-abi-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191118-ethereum-developer-abi-en/</guid>
      <description>Learn Ethereum development and acquire complex technical concepts in a snap!
Second State Inc is to release Ethereum development A2Z series articles to help you learn Ethereum in a short time starting from the basics, with real blockchain development cases.
This article is to introduce Smart Contract ABI, the first piece in the series.
Blockchain Smart Contract ABI is the interface between smart contracts and blockchain applications. After a smart contract is compiled into a binary file by a compiler like BUIDL, an ABI for this smart contract is automatically generated, recording the functions and parameters of the smart contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ABI | 以太坊开发A2Z </title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191112-ethereum-developer-abi-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191112-ethereum-developer-abi-zh/</guid>
      <description>快速了解以太坊开发，快速 get 复杂的技术概念！ Second State 推出以太坊开发A2Z 系列，结合区块链开发的实际情况，带你了解以太坊开发的点点面面。 这篇文章是该</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ewasm Vs EVM：Ewasm 带来了什么改变？</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191106-ewasm-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191106-ewasm-zh/</guid>
      <description>这篇文章是 Crosslink 2019 Taiwan 的一个议程纪录：The next generation Ethereum Virtual Machine，由来自Second State 的工程VP Hung-Ying Tai（hydai） 分享 Ewasm VM 目前研究内容及未来</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diving into Ethereum&#39;s Virtual Machine(EVM): the future of Ewasm</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191029-ewasm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191029-ewasm/</guid>
      <description>Ethereum is a blockchain with a built-in Turing-complete programming language. It allows anyone to create a decentralised application, by making use of Ethereum smart contracts.
 “The Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) is the part of Ethereum that handles smart contract deployment and execution” (Antonopoulos and Wood, 2018).
 The EVM consists of a stack-based architecture. In order for a smart contract to be deployed, all high level Ethereum smart contract code must first be compiled into machine-readable code (called bytecode).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>深度剖析以太坊虚拟机（EVM）的未来：Ewasm</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191029-ewasm-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191029-ewasm-zh/</guid>
      <description>以太坊是具有内置图灵完备编程语言的区块链。任何人都可以使用以太坊智能合约来创建去中心化应用程序。 “以太坊虚拟机（EVM）是以太坊处理智能合约</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compile and deploy an ERC20 contract on Ewasm</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191025-compile-and-deploy-an-erc20-contract-on-ewasm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191025-compile-and-deploy-an-erc20-contract-on-ewasm/</guid>
      <description>Second State provides open source infrastructure technologies for public and enterprise blockchains. The smart contract compiler toolchain and virtual machine runtimes are critical elements of the infrastructure.
Through its web-based BUIDL IDE, developers can easily access Second State smart contract programming languages, compilers, optimizers, and virtual machines. Even novice developers can write and publish decentralized applications (smart contract + web app) on any Ethereum-compatible blockchain in minutes. See examples on Ethereum Classic and CyberMiles blockchains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>一文带你了解Devcon5</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191025-devcon5-recap-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191025-devcon5-recap-zh/</guid>
      <description>以太坊基金会 Devcon 是以太坊生态系统中最重要的开发者、设计师和研究人员的年度聚会。今年在日本大阪举行的 Devcon5 是第五届以太开发大会，与往年一样，Devc</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I learned from Ethereum Devcon5</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191024-devcon5-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191024-devcon5-recap/</guid>
      <description>The Ethereum Foundation Devcon is the most important annual gathering of developers, designers, and researchers in the Ethereum ecosystem. This year’s Devcon5 in Osaka, Japan is the 5th Devcon, and as in past years, it is a bellwether of what to come in Ethereum.
Note: My company, Second State, was invited to give a talk at Devcon5, where we showed off the world&#39;s first toolchain to compile and deploy Solidity smart contracts on the official Ewasm testnet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State receives a prestigious award from the Ethereum Foundation for the SOLL compiler</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191022-soll-compiler-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191022-soll-compiler-project/</guid>
      <description>(Oct 20th, 2019, Taipei) - Second State, a leading provider of open source infrastructure software for blockchain smart contracts, has been awarded a cash prize for its contribution to the open source SOLL compiler project. Vitalik Buterin from the Ethereum Foundation presented Hung-Ying Tai from Second State with the $5000 prize at the CrossLink event in Taipei on Oct 20th, 2019.
SOLL is the world’s first toolchain that compiles Solidity smart contracts into WebAssembly bytecode and successfully deploys onto Ethereum Foundation’s official Ewasm (Ethereum flavored WebAssembly) testnet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State SOLL 编译器项目获得以太坊基金会的现金奖励</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191022-soll-compiler-project-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191022-soll-compiler-project-zh/</guid>
      <description>Second State 是领先的面向区块链智能合约的开源基础架构软件的提供者，因为对开源SOLL编译器项目的贡献，获得了以太坊基金会的现金奖励。2019年10月</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>