<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Solidity on Second State News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/solidity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Solidity on Second State News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 20:01:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/solidity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Polkadot is getting WebAssembly-based Ethereum 2.0 virtual machine from Second State</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200302-polkadot-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200302-polkadot-en/</guid>
      <description>Polkadot’s founder, Dr. Gavin Wood, is one of the original architects of the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM). Dr. Wood, the co-author of “Mastering Ethereum”, is also the author of the Ethereum yellow paper; a formal definition of the Ethereum protocol (in mathematical terms), which also provides an in-depth explanation of how the EVM actually works.
Some may be aware that the Polkadot ecosystem did not initially come with a Turing-complete virtual machine like the EVM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State awarded a grant to bring next-gen Ethereum infrastructure to Polkadot ecosystem</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200228-polkadot-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200228-polkadot-en/</guid>
      <description>(02/28/2020, Austin TX USA)The Web3 Foundation has awarded Second State, a leading cloud and blockchain infrastructure company, a grant to bring the Ethereum flavored WebAssembly (Ewasm) virtual machine to the Polkadot ecosystem. Get this project from GitHub here: https://github.com/second-state/substrate-ewasm
The virtual machine is a key infrastructure component for public blockchains. It allows any user from the public to submit untrusted code to the blockchain platform, in the form of smart contracts, and pay for its execution based on resource consumption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State 又获以太坊生态体系的资助奖励</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200217-soll-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200217-soll-zh/</guid>
      <description>Second State 最近获得了以太坊生态最大的去中心化自治组织（DAO） Panvala 的资助奖励。Panvala 由 ConsenSys 创立孵化，为以太坊生态里最重要的基础软件项目提供资金</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diving into Ethereum&#39;s Virtual Machine(EVM): the future of Ewasm</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191029-ewasm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191029-ewasm/</guid>
      <description>Ethereum is a blockchain with a built-in Turing-complete programming language. It allows anyone to create a decentralised application, by making use of Ethereum smart contracts.
 “The Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) is the part of Ethereum that handles smart contract deployment and execution” (Antonopoulos and Wood, 2018).
 The EVM consists of a stack-based architecture. In order for a smart contract to be deployed, all high level Ethereum smart contract code must first be compiled into machine-readable code (called bytecode).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>深度剖析以太坊虚拟机（EVM）的未来：Ewasm</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191029-ewasm-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191029-ewasm-zh/</guid>
      <description>以太坊是具有内置图灵完备编程语言的区块链。任何人都可以使用以太坊智能合约来创建去中心化应用程序。 “以太坊虚拟机（EVM）是以太坊处理智能合约</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State receives a prestigious award from the Ethereum Foundation for the SOLL compiler</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191022-soll-compiler-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191022-soll-compiler-project/</guid>
      <description>(Oct 20th, 2019, Taipei) - Second State, a leading provider of open source infrastructure software for blockchain smart contracts, has been awarded a cash prize for its contribution to the open source SOLL compiler project. Vitalik Buterin from the Ethereum Foundation presented Hung-Ying Tai from Second State with the $5000 prize at the CrossLink event in Taipei on Oct 20th, 2019.
SOLL is the world’s first toolchain that compiles Solidity smart contracts into WebAssembly bytecode and successfully deploys onto Ethereum Foundation’s official Ewasm (Ethereum flavored WebAssembly) testnet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State SOLL 编译器项目获得以太坊基金会的现金奖励</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191022-soll-compiler-project-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191022-soll-compiler-project-zh/</guid>
      <description>Second State 是领先的面向区块链智能合约的开源基础架构软件的提供者，因为对开源SOLL编译器项目的贡献，获得了以太坊基金会的现金奖励。2019年10月</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>