<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Second State News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Second State News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 10:01:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.secondstate.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>宅在家里上哈佛：450门常春藤盟校免费在线课程</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200327-stay-home-harvard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200327-stay-home-harvard/</guid>
      <description>安全第一哦，大家一起在家里学编程吧！英文原文戳→ https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ivy-league-free-online-courses-a0d7ae675869/ 美国新冠感染人数已经超过中国成为世界第一了。据约翰斯·霍普金斯大学数据，截至美东时间26日</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State joins Microsoft for Startups to develop the next generation software infrastructure for cloud computing</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200325-microsoft-for-startups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200325-microsoft-for-startups/</guid>
      <description>Second State joins the Microsoft for Startups program to develop and commercialize the next generation software infrastructure for cloud computing. With Microsoft for Startups, Second State will create open source software frameworks and developer tools for the cloud and for blockchains based on the WebAssembly technology.
WebAssembly was originally created as a high-performance execution engine for web browsers. As it becomes increasingly popular in the developer community, WebAssembly is moving from the client-side to the server-side, powering the next generation cloud services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polkadot is getting WebAssembly-based Ethereum 2.0 virtual machine from Second State</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200302-polkadot-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200302-polkadot-en/</guid>
      <description>Polkadot’s founder, Dr. Gavin Wood, is one of the original architects of the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM). Dr. Wood, the co-author of “Mastering Ethereum”, is also the author of the Ethereum yellow paper; a formal definition of the Ethereum protocol (in mathematical terms), which also provides an in-depth explanation of how the EVM actually works.
Some may be aware that the Polkadot ecosystem did not initially come with a Turing-complete virtual machine like the EVM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State awarded a grant to bring next-gen Ethereum infrastructure to Polkadot ecosystem</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200228-polkadot-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200228-polkadot-en/</guid>
      <description>(02/28/2020, Austin TX USA)The Web3 Foundation has awarded Second State, a leading cloud and blockchain infrastructure company, a grant to bring the Ethereum flavored WebAssembly (Ewasm) virtual machine to the Polkadot ecosystem. Get this project from GitHub here: https://github.com/second-state/substrate-ewasm
The virtual machine is a key infrastructure component for public blockchains. It allows any user from the public to submit untrusted code to the blockchain platform, in the form of smart contracts, and pay for its execution based on resource consumption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State 又获以太坊生态体系的资助奖励</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200217-soll-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200217-soll-zh/</guid>
      <description>Second State 最近获得了以太坊生态最大的去中心化自治组织（DAO） Panvala 的资助奖励。Panvala 由 ConsenSys 创立孵化，为以太坊生态里最重要的基础软件项目提供资金</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State receives another grant award for the SOLL compiler</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200216-soll-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200216-soll-en/</guid>
      <description>Second State has been awarded a development grant from Panvala, a leading DAO (Decentralized Autonomous Organization) in the Ethereum ecosystem.
Founded at ConsenSys, Panvala provides funding support for critical software development efforts in the Ethereum ecosystem. Past Panvala grant awardees include Sigma Prime, Prysmatic Labs, MakerDAO, Aragon, Status, and Gitcoin.
Prior to the Panvala grant, Second State is already a recognized leader in Ethereum infrastructure development. It is had received funding and grants from both the Ethereum Foundation and Ethereum Classic Labs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State releases WebAssembly for the server side</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191218-webassembly-for-the-server-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191218-webassembly-for-the-server-side/</guid>
      <description>An open source WebAssembly runtime optimized for blockchain, AI, and cloud services
(12/17/2019, Taipei)The Second State team has released a “developer preview” of the Second State Virtual Machine (SSVM). It is a WebAssembly (Wasm) compatible runtime engineered from ground up for server side applications. Get it from Github here: https://github.com/second-state/SSVM
Wasm started as a high performance execution engine inside web browsers. It is language agnostic (supporting popular new languages such as Rust), platform agnostic, lightweight, fast, and also provides native hardware access through its modular security model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>只需 5 分钟，教你如何编写并执行一个 Rust &#43; WebAssembly 程序</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191220-rust-webassembly-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191220-rust-webassembly-zh/</guid>
      <description>在探讨 WASM 在服务端的巨大潜力时，我们提到 WASM 的一大优势就是支持有影响力的新锐编程语言，例如 Rust 。这篇文章将展示如何编写并执行一个 Wasm Rust 程序，只有代码</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Ethereum Development A2Z| Smart Contract ABI </title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191118-ethereum-developer-abi-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191118-ethereum-developer-abi-en/</guid>
      <description>Learn Ethereum development and acquire complex technical concepts in a snap!
Second State Inc is to release Ethereum development A2Z series articles to help you learn Ethereum in a short time starting from the basics, with real blockchain development cases.
This article is to introduce Smart Contract ABI, the first piece in the series.
Blockchain Smart Contract ABI is the interface between smart contracts and blockchain applications. After a smart contract is compiled into a binary file by a compiler like BUIDL, an ABI for this smart contract is automatically generated, recording the functions and parameters of the smart contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ABI | 以太坊开发A2Z </title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191112-ethereum-developer-abi-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191112-ethereum-developer-abi-zh/</guid>
      <description>快速了解以太坊开发，快速 get 复杂的技术概念！ Second State 推出以太坊开发A2Z 系列，结合区块链开发的实际情况，带你了解以太坊开发的点点面面。 这篇文章是该</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Next Generation Ethereum Virtual Machine — Ewasm VM</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191106-ewasm-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191106-ewasm-en/</guid>
      <description>The next generation Ethereum Virtual Machine — Crosslink 2019 Taiwan This is a wrap-up for Second State’s VP of Engineering, Mr. Hung-Ying Tai’s presentation on SOLL, Ewasm VM&#39;s current research content and future direction. The sharing is very exciting, including content on EVM bytecode, Webassembly, Ewasm1.0 and Ewasm2.0 EVM bytecode and Webassembly (WASM) When Ethereum&#39;s smart contract transaction is executed,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ewasm Vs EVM：Ewasm 带来了什么改变？</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191106-ewasm-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191106-ewasm-zh/</guid>
      <description>这篇文章是 Crosslink 2019 Taiwan 的一个议程纪录：The next generation Ethereum Virtual Machine，由来自Second State 的工程VP Hung-Ying Tai（hydai） 分享 Ewasm VM 目前研究内容及未来</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State(第二形科技) 亮相世界级区块链技术盛会旧金山区块链周</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191031-sfbw-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191031-sfbw-zh/</guid>
      <description>备受瞩目的世界级区块链技术盛会-旧金山区块链周于当地时间10月28日拉开帷幕，区块链基础软件技术公司Second State(第二形科技) 赞助</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrate Halloween with Blockchain Smart Contract</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191031-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191031-halloween/</guid>
      <description>Halloween is finally here! Are you ready for the spookiest night of the year?
BUIDL IDE tools now has an upgraded UI just for Halloween. Trick or treat! A spooky pumpkin on the top welcomes you to the BUIDL’s Halloween.
Now, for developers, can you tell what the following code is for?
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8  pragma lity ^1.2.4; contract Halloween { function greet() pure public returns (string) { return &amp;#34;Happy Halloween&amp;#34;; } }   This is a very simple (yet spooky) smart contract example, just like the “Hello World” on the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diving into Ethereum&#39;s Virtual Machine(EVM): the future of Ewasm</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191029-ewasm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191029-ewasm/</guid>
      <description>Ethereum is a blockchain with a built-in Turing-complete programming language. It allows anyone to create a decentralised application, by making use of Ethereum smart contracts.
 “The Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) is the part of Ethereum that handles smart contract deployment and execution” (Antonopoulos and Wood, 2018).
 The EVM consists of a stack-based architecture. In order for a smart contract to be deployed, all high level Ethereum smart contract code must first be compiled into machine-readable code (called bytecode).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>深度剖析以太坊虚拟机（EVM）的未来：Ewasm</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191029-ewasm-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191029-ewasm-zh/</guid>
      <description>以太坊是具有内置图灵完备编程语言的区块链。任何人都可以使用以太坊智能合约来创建去中心化应用程序。 “以太坊虚拟机（EVM）是以太坊处理智能合约</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build your own decentralized website with BUIDL IDE</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191025-build-your-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191025-build-your-website/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever tried to build your own website?
You need to
 Get Web Hosting Register a Domain name(usually ~$15/year) Set up your website from the web host ········  Way too many steps! But with BUIDL IDE tools, you can build a decentralized website all by yourself in 5 minutes. The website will not only allow you to write any words you want but also allow your friends to access this page and interact with you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compile and deploy an ERC20 contract on Ewasm</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191025-compile-and-deploy-an-erc20-contract-on-ewasm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191025-compile-and-deploy-an-erc20-contract-on-ewasm/</guid>
      <description>Second State provides open source infrastructure technologies for public and enterprise blockchains. The smart contract compiler toolchain and virtual machine runtimes are critical elements of the infrastructure.
Through its web-based BUIDL IDE, developers can easily access Second State smart contract programming languages, compilers, optimizers, and virtual machines. Even novice developers can write and publish decentralized applications (smart contract + web app) on any Ethereum-compatible blockchain in minutes. See examples on Ethereum Classic and CyberMiles blockchains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>一文带你了解Devcon5</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191025-devcon5-recap-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191025-devcon5-recap-zh/</guid>
      <description>以太坊基金会 Devcon 是以太坊生态系统中最重要的开发者、设计师和研究人员的年度聚会。今年在日本大阪举行的 Devcon5 是第五届以太开发大会，与往年一样，Devc</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I learned from Ethereum Devcon5</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191024-devcon5-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191024-devcon5-recap/</guid>
      <description>The Ethereum Foundation Devcon is the most important annual gathering of developers, designers, and researchers in the Ethereum ecosystem. This year’s Devcon5 in Osaka, Japan is the 5th Devcon, and as in past years, it is a bellwether of what to come in Ethereum.
Note: My company, Second State, was invited to give a talk at Devcon5, where we showed off the world&#39;s first toolchain to compile and deploy Solidity smart contracts on the official Ewasm testnet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>