<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rust on Second State News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/rust/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rust on Second State News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 06:42:14 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/rust/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The SSVM 0.7 release brings WebAssembly to the public cloud</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20210202-ssvm-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 06:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20210202-ssvm-release/</guid>
      <description>The SSVM (Second State VM) is a popular WebAssembly VM optimized for high-performance applications on the server side. With advanced AOT (Ahead of Time compiler) support, the SSVM is already one of the fastest WebAssembly VMs. The recent SSVM release 0.7 brings a wide array of unique features that further differentiate and solidify the SSVM as a leading cloud native application runtime.
WebAssembly proposals The SSVM supports optional WebAssembly features and proposals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State Functions releases a developer preview for high performance serverless functions</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20210114-second-state-functions-developer-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 06:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20210114-second-state-functions-developer-preview/</guid>
      <description>Second State has recently released a developer preview of its Function-as-a-Service (FaaS), known as Second State Functions. The Second State Functions enables developers to write simple functions in the Rust programming language for computationally intensive tasks such as image processing and AI inference. The developer simply needs to upload the compiled function to the FaaS service, and the function will become publically available as a web service. The developer preview version of the Second State Functions is free to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSVM 0.7.0：朝更具互操作性的 WebAssembly 迈进</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201028-toward-a-more-interoperable-webassembly-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201028-toward-a-more-interoperable-webassembly-zh/</guid>
      <description>Second State 虚拟机 0.7.0 版本支持 reference types 和 bulk memory operations。 Second State 虚拟机（SSVM）是针对服务器端应用优化的开源 WebAssembly 虚拟机实现。 SSVM 是当今市场上最快的 WebAssembly 虚</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toward a more interoperable WebAssembly</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201026-toward-a-more-interoperable-webassembly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201026-toward-a-more-interoperable-webassembly/</guid>
      <description>Interface types and bulk memory operations support on Second State VM 0.7.0
 TL;DR Second State is committed to support the vision of WebAssembly nanoprocess proposed by Bytecode Alliance, Fastly, and Mozilla. SSVM 0.7.0 implements two key components of nanoprocess: WASI and Interface Types. We are taking it further with WASI-like extensions for blockchains and Tensorflow. Try our Tensorflow as a Service live demo today!
 The Second State VM (SSVM) is an open-source WebAssembly virtual machine implementation optimized for server-side applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State releases scalable privacy service at Mozilla Open Labs</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200603-scalable-privacy-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200603-scalable-privacy-service/</guid>
      <description>Building a scalable and privacy-first Internet on Second State’s serverless infrastructure. Get the email newsletter on Rust, WebAssembly, serverless, blockchain, and AI.
Internet privacy is broken The Public Key Infrastructure (PKI), invented over 40 years ago, has been the bed rock for security and privacy on the Internet. While PKI algorithms are behind the most internet security protocols, such as HTTPS and TLS, the idea for individuals to use public keys to exchange data, (eg, PGP), was not adopted in large scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Rust</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200529-why-rust-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 19:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200529-why-rust-en/</guid>
      <description>The Rust programming language is gaining popularity amongst developers. For 5 years in a row, it is voted as the most beloved programming language in the world. In the most recent 2020 survey of 65,000 developers, Rust was beloved by a stunning 86.1% of developers. Being loved by developers is a leading indicator that Rust is on the path of mass adoption. It is entering a positive feedback cycle of more developers, more libraries, better tools, larger talent pool, more adoption, and then more developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>只需 5 分钟，教你如何编写并执行一个 Rust &#43; WebAssembly 程序</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191220-rust-webassembly-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191220-rust-webassembly-zh/</guid>
      <description>在探讨 WASM 在服务端的巨大潜力时，我们提到 WASM 的一大优势就是支持有影响力的新锐编程语言，例如 Rust 。这篇文章将展示如何编写并执行一个 Wasm Rust 程序，只有代码</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebAssembly on the server side</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191124-wasm-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 19:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191124-wasm-en/</guid>
      <description>WebAssembly (Wasm), originally invented and developed by Mozilla, Google, Microsoft, Apple, and others at W3C; is a high-performance execution engine for in-browser web applications. As it gains popularity on the client-side, Wasm is also becoming a serious contender as a server-side technology.
Value propositions of WebAssembly Wasm’s move from client-side to server-side follows well-traveled paths of previous generations of technologies such as Java and JavaScript. Compared with existing solutions, Wasm offers some compelling value propositions on the server-side.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>