<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Buidl on Second State News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/buidl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Buidl on Second State News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 09:42:14 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/buidl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> Ethereum Development A2Z| Smart Contract ABI </title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191118-ethereum-developer-abi-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191118-ethereum-developer-abi-en/</guid>
      <description>Learn Ethereum development and acquire complex technical concepts in a snap!
Second State Inc is to release Ethereum development A2Z series articles to help you learn Ethereum in a short time starting from the basics, with real blockchain development cases.
This article is to introduce Smart Contract ABI, the first piece in the series.
Blockchain Smart Contract ABI is the interface between smart contracts and blockchain applications. After a smart contract is compiled into a binary file by a compiler like BUIDL, an ABI for this smart contract is automatically generated, recording the functions and parameters of the smart contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ABI | 以太坊开发A2Z </title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191112-ethereum-developer-abi-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191112-ethereum-developer-abi-zh/</guid>
      <description>快速了解以太坊开发，快速 get 复杂的技术概念！ Second State 推出以太坊开发A2Z 系列，结合区块链开发的实际情况，带你了解以太坊开发的点点面面。 这篇文章是该</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State(第二形科技) 亮相世界级区块链技术盛会旧金山区块链周</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191031-sfbw-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191031-sfbw-zh/</guid>
      <description>备受瞩目的世界级区块链技术盛会-旧金山区块链周于当地时间10月28日拉开帷幕，区块链基础软件技术公司Second State(第二形科技) 赞助</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build your own decentralized website with BUIDL IDE</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191025-build-your-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191025-build-your-website/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever tried to build your own website?
You need to
 Get Web Hosting Register a Domain name(usually ~$15/year) Set up your website from the web host ········  Way too many steps! But with BUIDL IDE tools, you can build a decentralized website all by yourself in 5 minutes. The website will not only allow you to write any words you want but also allow your friends to access this page and interact with you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>教程|5分钟建一个去中心化的网站</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191024-build-website-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191024-build-website-zh/</guid>
      <description>不用买域名，购买虚拟主机空间，设置域名服务器，工信部备案等等繁琐的流程。 5分钟学会自己建一个去中心化的网站，从此做网站不求人！永久留存，完全</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>如何使用BUIDL 发起投票议题</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191020-public-comment-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191020-public-comment-zh/</guid>
      <description>在区块链世界里，您留下的评论会永远留存，不能被篡改，永远不会消失~ DApp小科普 区块链应用（DApp）通常以智能合约为后端，以HTML 和 Ja</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETC 峰会回顾：未来可期</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191006-etc-summit-recap-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191006-etc-summit-recap-zh/</guid>
      <description>声明：Second State赞助了今年的ETC峰会，并发布了ETC 版BUIDL IDE。有了BUIDL，即便是菜鸟开发者都可以在几分钟内在以太</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I learned from ETC Summit</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191006-etc-summit-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191006-etc-summit-recap/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: Second State sponsored this year’s ETC Summit and released the BUIDL for ETC IDE — even novice developers can now write and publish complete smart contract powered applications on the Ethereum Classic blockchain in minutes. Check out a tutorial! All views and opinions expressed in the article are my own. 中文版点击这里 Church &amp;amp; State Successful open source communities</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easier and faster dapps on the Ethereum Classic blockchain</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191003-easierandfasterdapps-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191003-easierandfasterdapps-en/</guid>
      <description>Ethereum, the world’s first and dominant smart contract platform, has the largest dapp ecosystem with more than a million deployed smart contracts and hundreds of millions of dollars in monthly transactions.
Ethereum Classic is the original Ethereum blockchain. With fast confirmation time, ultra-low gas cost, and now with first-class developer tooling from the BUIDL IDE, the Ethereum Classic blockchain is also becoming the best platform for deploying smart contracts and dapps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treasure Hunt -- Ethereum Classic Edition</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191002-book-etc-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191002-book-etc-en/</guid>
      <description>The Building Blockchain Apps book is to be published by Addison-Wesley in 2019. It provides a comprehensive guide for developers to incorporate the blockchain technology into existing and future applications. You can pre-order it from Amazon or InformIT.
How to get the 35% discount code The discount code is “hidden in plain sight” in a smart contract deployed on the Ethereum Classic blockchain. Using BUIDL for ETC, you can instantiate an instance of this contract and call it’s functions to get its state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling All Developers: Second State Launches BUIDL IDE, an Integrated Development Environment Software Application, for Ethereum Classic Blockchain</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190925-buidl-for-etc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190925-buidl-for-etc/</guid>
      <description>This news is also seen on PRweb.com
 SAN FRANCISCO (Sept. 24, 2019) —Second State, developer of an open source, blockchain-based smart contract platform for global business, has announced the launch of its BUIDL IDE, an integrated development environment software application for Ethereum Classic (ETC), the preeminent blockchain for smart contracts and “dapps.” With Second State’s BUIDL IDE, development and deployment on ETC can be done within minutes, from any web browser: secondstate.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>