<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Book on Second State News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/book/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book on Second State News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 01:01:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Easier and faster dapps on the Ethereum Classic blockchain</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191003-easierandfasterdapps-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191003-easierandfasterdapps-en/</guid>
      <description>Ethereum, the world’s first and dominant smart contract platform, has the largest dapp ecosystem with more than a million deployed smart contracts and hundreds of millions of dollars in monthly transactions.
Ethereum Classic is the original Ethereum blockchain. With fast confirmation time, ultra-low gas cost, and now with first-class developer tooling from the BUIDL IDE, the Ethereum Classic blockchain is also becoming the best platform for deploying smart contracts and dapps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treasure Hunt -- Ethereum Classic Edition</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191002-book-etc-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191002-book-etc-en/</guid>
      <description>The Building Blockchain Apps book is to be published by Addison-Wesley in 2019. It provides a comprehensive guide for developers to incorporate the blockchain technology into existing and future applications. You can pre-order it from Amazon or InformIT.
How to get the 35% discount code The discount code is “hidden in plain sight” in a smart contract deployed on the Ethereum Classic blockchain. Using BUIDL for ETC, you can instantiate an instance of this contract and call it’s functions to get its state.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>