<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hackathon on Second State News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/hackathon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hackathon on Second State News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 06:42:14 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/hackathon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State Functions releases a developer preview for high performance serverless functions</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20210114-second-state-functions-developer-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 06:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20210114-second-state-functions-developer-preview/</guid>
      <description>Second State has recently released a developer preview of its Function-as-a-Service (FaaS), known as Second State Functions. The Second State Functions enables developers to write simple functions in the Rust programming language for computationally intensive tasks such as image processing and AI inference. The developer simply needs to upload the compiled function to the FaaS service, and the function will become publically available as a web service. The developer preview version of the Second State Functions is free to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State partners with Oasis Foundation and Gitcoin to host The Quest for ROSE</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201109-secondstate-oasis-gitcoin-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 06:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201109-secondstate-oasis-gitcoin-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>Developers rejoice! A new week, a new hackathon with great prizes!
The Oasis Foundation announced the Quest for ROSE: An Oasis Network Hackathon in partnership with Gitcoin and Second State from 9th November to 2nd December.
There are two challenges for the Quest for ROSE hackathon. One is to use Parcel SDK of Oasis Network to develop responsible data apps. The other one is to use Oasis Ethereum ParaTimeto develop ethereum-compatible Dapps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developers created 3274 smart contracts in the Oasis Second State Hackathon</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201029-recap-the-oasis-second-state-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 06:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20201029-recap-the-oasis-second-state-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>Oasis Foundation and Second State partnered on a community hackathon from 12th to 23rd Oct to bring Ethereum developers to the Oasis Ethereum ParaTime. Now, the results are in! Community developers created 3274 smart contracts and published 759 decentralized web apps in 11 days!
The Oasis Second State Hackathon set up three challenges for developers to complete. When developers complete any of the challenges, they get ROSE (the native token of the Oasis network) as rewards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Oasis Second State Community Hackathon starts</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/oasis-secondstate-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/oasis-secondstate-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>Today Second State, together with Oasis foundation, is announcing the most exciting community event to date, and a chance for community members to earn some of the largest rewards Oasis foundation has ever offered. Last week Oasis network launched Mainnet Beta, and we released Second State’s Oasis Ethereum ParaTime.
The ParaTime’s powerful design and technology means the Oasis Ethereum ParaTime is:
 Completely backward compatible with Ethereum with support for the entire Solidity toolchain, allowing it to support DApps currently on the Ethereum network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>奖励最高达 31050 ROSE, Oasis &#43; Second State 线上 Hackathon 正式开始</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/oasis-secondstate-hackathon-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/oasis-secondstate-hackathon-zh/</guid>
      <description>发布Dapp，在 Oasis network 上运行以太坊智能合约，就可以获得 ROSE Token 奖励 Oasis Network 是隐私计算领域的知名项目，10月2日，Oasis 基金会发布了 Mainnet beta 版以及由 Second State</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>