<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business on Second State News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business on Second State News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 15:01:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How does rules engine help the blockchain adoption</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190510-howrulesenginehelps-theblockchainapplication-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 15:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190510-howrulesenginehelps-theblockchainapplication-en/</guid>
      <description>When you want to integrate blockchain into your business but you dont have so much development resources, do you just give up?
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry! Rules engine comes to rescue!
What is a rule engine?
Is a component embedded in the application that separates business decisions from the code applied.
The core of the rules engine is to obtain knowledge (knowledge) Apply knowledge to specific data (fact) Use &amp;ldquo;production rules&amp;rdquo; IF  THEN  Rule expression logic (any logic can be expressed this way)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The lean blockchain startup — a new strategy to grow and prosper!</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190319-lean/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 16:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190319-lean/</guid>
      <description>The concept behind a &amp;ldquo;lean startup&amp;rdquo; is to grow an innovative business idea, as fast as possible, with as little as possible.
 The overall goal is to grow and prosper!
 Creating a lean initiative, however, does not mean “going without.” On the contrary, a lean initiative is about getting more bang for your buck. This is achieved by making better decisions. Better decisions though cannot be made using yesterday’s knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>