<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WebAssembly on Second State News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/webassembly/</link>
    <description>Recent content in WebAssembly on Second State News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 10:01:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.secondstate.io/tags/webassembly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State releases scalable privacy service at Mozilla Open Labs</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200603-scalable-privacy-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200603-scalable-privacy-service/</guid>
      <description>Building a scalable and privacy-first Internet on Second State’s serverless infrastructure. Get the email newsletter on Rust, WebAssembly, serverless, blockchain, and AI.
Internet privacy is broken The Public Key Infrastructure (PKI), invented over 40 years ago, has been the bed rock for security and privacy on the Internet. While PKI algorithms are behind the most internet security protocols, such as HTTPS and TLS, the idea for individuals to use public keys to exchange data, (eg, PGP), was not adopted in large scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>宅在家里上哈佛：450门常春藤盟校免费在线课程</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200327-stay-home-harvard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200327-stay-home-harvard/</guid>
      <description>安全第一哦，大家一起在家里学编程吧！ 美国新冠感染人数已经超过中国成为世界第一了。据约翰斯·霍普金斯大学数据，截至美东时间26日17时37分，</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State joins Microsoft for Startups to develop the next generation software infrastructure for cloud computing</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200325-microsoft-for-startups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200325-microsoft-for-startups/</guid>
      <description>Second State joins the Microsoft for Startups program to develop and commercialize the next generation software infrastructure for cloud computing. With Microsoft for Startups, Second State will create open source software frameworks and developer tools for the cloud and for blockchains based on the WebAssembly technology.
WebAssembly was originally created as a high-performance execution engine for web browsers. As it becomes increasingly popular in the developer community, WebAssembly is moving from the client-side to the server-side, powering the next generation cloud services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polkadot is getting WebAssembly-based Ethereum 2.0 virtual machine from Second State</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200302-polkadot-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200302-polkadot-en/</guid>
      <description>Polkadot’s founder, Dr. Gavin Wood, is one of the original architects of the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM). Dr. Wood, the co-author of “Mastering Ethereum”, is also the author of the Ethereum yellow paper; a formal definition of the Ethereum protocol (in mathematical terms), which also provides an in-depth explanation of how the EVM actually works.
Some may be aware that the Polkadot ecosystem did not initially come with a Turing-complete virtual machine like the EVM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State awarded a grant to bring next-gen Ethereum infrastructure to Polkadot ecosystem</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200228-polkadot-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 20:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20200228-polkadot-en/</guid>
      <description>(02/28/2020, Austin TX USA)The Web3 Foundation has awarded Second State, a leading cloud and blockchain infrastructure company, a grant to bring the Ethereum flavored WebAssembly (Ewasm) virtual machine to the Polkadot ecosystem. Get this project from GitHub here: https://github.com/second-state/substrate-ewasm
The virtual machine is a key infrastructure component for public blockchains. It allows any user from the public to submit untrusted code to the blockchain platform, in the form of smart contracts, and pay for its execution based on resource consumption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State releases WebAssembly for the server side</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191218-webassembly-for-the-server-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191218-webassembly-for-the-server-side/</guid>
      <description>An open source WebAssembly runtime optimized for blockchain, AI, and cloud services
(12/17/2019, Taipei)The Second State team has released a “developer preview” of the Second State Virtual Machine (SSVM). It is a WebAssembly (Wasm) compatible runtime engineered from ground up for server side applications. Get it from Github here: https://github.com/second-state/SSVM
Wasm started as a high performance execution engine inside web browsers. It is language agnostic (supporting popular new languages such as Rust), platform agnostic, lightweight, fast, and also provides native hardware access through its modular security model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>只需 5 分钟，教你如何编写并执行一个 Rust &#43; WebAssembly 程序</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191220-rust-webassembly-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 09:42:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191220-rust-webassembly-zh/</guid>
      <description>在探讨 WASM 在服务端的巨大潜力时，我们提到 WASM 的一大优势就是支持有影响力的新锐编程语言，例如 Rust 。这篇文章将展示如何编写并执行一个 Wasm Rust 程序，只有代码</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebAssembly on the server side</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191124-wasm-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 19:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191124-wasm-en/</guid>
      <description>WebAssembly (Wasm), originally invented and developed by Mozilla, Google, Microsoft, Apple, and others at W3C; is a high-performance execution engine for in-browser web applications. As it gains popularity on the client-side, Wasm is also becoming a serious contender as a server-side technology.
Value propositions of WebAssembly Wasm’s move from client-side to server-side follows well-traveled paths of previous generations of technologies such as Java and JavaScript. Compared with existing solutions, Wasm offers some compelling value propositions on the server-side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State receives a prestigious award from the Ethereum Foundation for the SOLL compiler</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191022-soll-compiler-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191022-soll-compiler-project/</guid>
      <description>(Oct 20th, 2019, Taipei) - Second State, a leading provider of open source infrastructure software for blockchain smart contracts, has been awarded a cash prize for its contribution to the open source SOLL compiler project. Vitalik Buterin from the Ethereum Foundation presented Hung-Ying Tai from Second State with the $5000 prize at the CrossLink event in Taipei on Oct 20th, 2019.
SOLL is the world’s first toolchain that compiles Solidity smart contracts into WebAssembly bytecode and successfully deploys onto Ethereum Foundation’s official Ewasm (Ethereum flavored WebAssembly) testnet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State SOLL 编译器项目获得以太坊基金会的现金奖励</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191022-soll-compiler-project-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 01:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20191022-soll-compiler-project-zh/</guid>
      <description>Second State 是领先的面向区块链智能合约的开源基础架构软件的提供者，因为对开源SOLL编译器项目的贡献，获得了以太坊基金会的现金奖励。2019年10月</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second State 入围高通台湾创新赛，用企业中间件推动区块链芯片变革</title>
      <link>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190826-blockchain-chips-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.secondstate.io/post/20190826-blockchain-chips-zh/</guid>
      <description>中国芯片危机由来已久。近期，随着贸易战的持续加剧，“振兴”中国芯片迫在眉睫，势在必行。 “昨天”的芯片战场是以智能手机为代表的移动互联网应用，</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>